{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below is used to describe a foundational level of security configurations and settings required to safeguard a system?",
      "options": [
        "Logical segmentation",
        "Secure baseline",
        "Access control levels",
        "Principle of least privilege"
      ],
      "correct_answers": ["Secure baseline"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Installing mobile apps from trusted sources (e.g., Apple's App Store for iOS devices, or Google Play for Android devices) instead of third-party application stores decreases malware-related security risks.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Data on a lost or stolen mobile device can be erased by:",
      "options": ["Rooting", "Sideloading", "Low-level formatting", "Remote wipe"],
      "correct_answers": ["Remote wipe"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a mobile security solution that enables separate controls over the user and enterprise data?",
      "options": [
        "Resource provisioning",
        "Content management",
        "Storage segmentation",
        "Just-in-time permissions"
      ],
      "correct_answers": ["Storage segmentation"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Implementing full device encryption is one of the methods for securing sensitive data on a smartphone. When enabled, this type of encryption works in conjunction with the phone's screen lock, i.e., to decrypt the phone (which stays encrypted whenever the phone is locked), a user must first unlock the screen. On Android devices, the unlocking methods include entering a PIN, password, or drawing a simple pattern with a finger. Apple devices use passcodes, facial recognition (Face ID), and fingerprint (Touch ID).",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "In the context of MDM, the isolation of corporate applications and data from other parts of the mobile device is referred to as:",
      "options": ["Containerization", "Storage segmentation", "Virtualization", "Content management"],
      "correct_answers": ["Containerization"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refer to workstation hardening techniques? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Hiding administrator accounts",
        "Regularly applying security patches and updates to the OS and installed software",
        "Disabling all internet access",
        "Removing or disabling unnecessary drivers, services, software, and network protocols",
        "Limiting unauthorized or unauthenticated user access"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Regularly applying security patches and updates to the OS and installed software",
        "Removing or disabling unnecessary drivers, services, software, and network protocols",
        "Limiting unauthorized or unauthenticated user access"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refer(s) to (a) router hardening technique(s)? (Select all that apply)",
      "options": [
        "Changing default credentials",
        "Disabling unused services and ports",
        "Changing device name",
        "Disabling the broadcasting of the router's SSID",
        "Implementing regular firmware updates"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Changing default credentials",
        "Disabling unused services and ports",
        "Implementing regular firmware updates"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to the process of assessing the physical environment, such as the layout of the building, to identify potential sources of interference and determine the optimal placement of a WAP?",
      "options": ["Gap analysis", "Capacity planning", "Site survey", "Vulnerability scanning"],
      "correct_answers": ["Site survey"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An administrator needs to adjust the placement of multiple APs to ensure the best wireless signal coverage for the network. Which of the following would be of help in identifying areas of low signal strength?",
      "options": ["Heat map", "Power level controls", "Logical network diagram", "Wi-Fi hotspots"],
      "correct_answers": ["Heat map"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which type of software allows centralized control over the configuration, monitoring, and security of mobile devices used within an organization?",
      "options": ["MDR", "IAM", "SIEM", "MDM"],
      "correct_answers": ["MDM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to software that facilitates the enforcement of mobile device policies and procedures?",
      "options": ["NAC", "MDM", "XDR", "PAM"],
      "correct_answers": ["MDM"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A mobile device deployment model that allows employees to use private mobile devices for accessing the company's restricted data and applications is known as:",
      "options": ["COPE", "BYOD", "MDM", "CYOD"],
      "correct_answers": ["BYOD"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a mobile device deployment model where organizations provide and own the devices while allowing their personal use?",
      "options": ["BYOD", "COPE", "ZTA", "CYOD"],
      "correct_answers": ["COPE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a mobile device deployment model in which employees select devices for work-related tasks from a company-approved device list?",
      "options": ["CYOD", "UEM", "BYOD", "COPE"],
      "correct_answers": ["CYOD"]
    },
    {
      "question": "An SSID is a unique identifier (a.k.a. wireless network name) for a WLAN. Wireless networks advertise their presence by regularly broadcasting SSID in a special packet called beacon frame. In wireless networks with disabled security features, knowing the network SSID is enough to get access to the network. SSID also pinpoints the wireless router that acts as a WAP. Wireless routers from the same manufacturer are frequently configured with default (well-known) SSID names. Since multiple devices with the same SSID displayed on the list of available networks create confusion and encourage accidental access by unauthorized users (applies to networks that lack security), changing the default SSID is a recommended practice.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "For a wireless client to be able to connect to a network, the security type (e.g., WEP, WPA, WPA2, or WPA3) and encryption type (e.g., TKIP or AES) settings on the connecting host must match the corresponding wireless security settings on a WAP.",
      "options": ["True", "False"],
      "correct_answers": ["True"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a security feature used in Bluetooth device pairing?",
      "options": ["SAE", "PIN", "MFA", "ACL"],
      "correct_answers": ["PIN"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following solutions would offer the strongest security for a small network that lacks an authentication server?",
      "options": ["WPA3-SAE", "WPA2-Enterprise", "WPA2-PSK", "WPA3-Enterprise"],
      "correct_answers": ["WPA3-SAE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the characteristic features of WPA2/WPA3 Enterprise mode? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Suitable for large corporate networks",
        "IEEE 802.1D",
        "Does not require an authentication server",
        "IEEE 802.1X",
        "Suitable for all types of wireless LANs",
        "Requires RADIUS authentication server"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Suitable for large corporate networks",
        "IEEE 802.1X",
        "Requires RADIUS authentication server"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of the encryption protocol primarily used in Wi-Fi networks implementing the WPA3 security standard?",
      "options": ["AES-CCMP", "CBC-MAC", "AES-GCMP", "WPA-TKIP"],
      "correct_answers": ["AES-GCMP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following acronyms refers to a client authentication method used in WPA3 Personal mode?",
      "options": ["SAE", "IKE", "PSK", "AES"],
      "correct_answers": ["SAE"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the characteristics of TACACS+? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Encrypts only the password in the access-request packet",
        "Combines authentication and authorization",
        "Encrypts the entire payload of the access-request packet",
        "Primarily used for device administration",
        "Separates authentication and authorization",
        "Primarily used for network access"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Encrypts the entire payload of the access-request packet",
        "Primarily used for device administration",
        "Separates authentication and authorization"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "What are the characteristic features of RADIUS? (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Primarily used for network access",
        "Encrypts the entire payload of the access-request packet",
        "Combines authentication and authorization",
        "Encrypts only the password in the access-request packet",
        "Primarily used for device administration",
        "Separates authentication and authorization"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Primarily used for network access",
        "Combines authentication and authorization",
        "Encrypts only the password in the access-request packet"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the wireless encryption schemes listed below offers the highest level of protection?",
      "options": ["WPS", "WPA3", "AES", "TKIP"],
      "correct_answers": ["WPA3"]
    }
  ]
}